(Sheldon:)I hope that's a rhetorical question
because I have no clue.
Mm. This is great, what's the occasion?
(Leonard:)No occasion.
Things have been a little weird between us...
(Leonard:)...so I wanted to throw together
a fun night for you.
- That is so sweet.
- I got your favorites:
(Leonard:)Beer, wings, sliders, we can watch
the football game. I even painted my stomach.
- Go sports?
- Well?
(Leonard:)In case you were in the mood for baseball,
I didn't wanna look ridiculous.
- This is awesome, I love it.
- Good, I'm glad.
(Penny:)I worked my ass off,
so this is what I needed.
(Leonard:)Great, just relax and enjoy.
Tonight is all about you.
(Penny:)Ah. Thank you.
(Leonard:)So where exactly are we
in this relationship?
(Penny:)Oh, come on, I just told you
I had a hard day.
- You're right, I'm sorry. Let's watch the game.
- Great.
(Leonard:)Just know, the longer we wait
to talk about it the weirder it gets.